smarterasp.net 2017-06-06

# SmarterASP.net - Privacy policy

SmarterASP.net is committed to protect our customer's privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our privacy practices with regard to the information that we collect when you interact with our website and services. By accessing SmarterASP.net website and services, you consent to the information collection and use described within. 

**Third Party Vendors**  
Third party vendor sites that are included or used as part of the SmarterASP.net services have their own privacy policies and you acknowledge that SmarterASP.net has no control over third party policies and is not responsible for their privacy practices. 

**Information Disclosure**  
SmarterASP.net will not disclose or share personally identifiable information with third parties without your permission except when necessary to provide resolution to a service request, to comply with federal or state law or subpeonas, or to comply with liquidation or mergers and acquisition-related activities. 

**Aggregate Statistics**  
SmarterASP.net may share aggregate statistical information regarding its customers, including survey results, with partners or other third parties. In no way, will this information be personally identifiable. 

**Personal Information**  
Users can purchase SmarterASP.net services by completing our online order forms. As part of the order form, we will request personal contact information and financial information. Any contact information is used to contact the customer to provide our services and any financial information is used only to bill for the SmarterASP.net services purchased. 

**Secure Forms**  
When collecting personally identifiable information, we use forms protected by industry standard secure sockets layer (ssl) technology. Using SSL protected forms, all personally identifiable information is encrypted during data transport. 

**Cookies, Website Stats, Image Markers and other Tracking Software**  
SmarterASP.net uses cookies, website traffic statistics, image markers, visitor IP address, and other tracking software to help improve our website, services, and marketing effectiveness. For example, we use cookies to analyze repeat visits to our website, we use website statistics to analyze how visitors use and interact with our website and other web properties, we use image markers in email campaigns to understand how many users opened a particular email message, and we use other tracking tools to measure advertising effectiveness. 

SmarterASP.net uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Opt-out**  
SmarterASP.net provides an opt-out option for customers who purchase a product or service from SmarterASP.net to unsubscribe from news, announcements and marketing marterial that we may send to customers from time to time. An unsubscribe link is located at the bottom of all announcement and marketing emails that we send out. If a customer no longer wishes to receive SmarterASP.net newsletters, news, announcements, and promotional email, they may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in such emails and opting out through their control panel. 

**Policy Changes**  
SmarterASP.net may update this privacy policy in its sole discretion. When updated, we will revise the "Last update" date at the bottom of this page. Your continued use of the website and service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updates. 

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy or its implementation, please Contact US and our Sales team will route your inquiry to the appropriate staff member. 

Last Update: July 5, 2012
